Guide to the Norma L. Kelsey Papers
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
Norma L. Kelsey papers
approximately 1970-2010
University of Washington Libraries Special Collections Box 352900 Seattle, WA 98195-2900
6231
Kelsey, Norma L.
12.66 cubic feet 11 boxes
Papers and VHS tapes of a labor activist, social justice activist, feminist, and union member
Labor activist, social justice activist, feminist, and union member. Kelsey was a member or officer of various labor and social justice organizations, including the Office and Professional Employees International Union Local 8, the King County Labor Council; El Centro de la Raza; Mothers for Police Accountability, the King County Union Retirees Council, the Puget Sound Alliance for Retired Americans, and the Coalition of Labor Union Women, among others. Kelsey was also involved in the work of the Seattle City Council's World Trade Organization Accountability Review Committee as a member of its Citizens Panel on Planning and Preparedness.
Organized into 2 accessions.
Accession No. 6231-001, Norma L. Kelsey papers, 1970s-2010s
Accession No. 6231-002, Norma L. Kelsey video recordings and papers, approximately 1990-2010
Correspondence, materials related to Kelsey's activism with labor and social justice organizations, records of her membership in Local 8, boad records, interview notes, draft documents, reports, VHS tapes, and print material related to OPEIU Local 8 meetings.
No restrictions on access.
Donated by Norma Kelsey.
Kelsey, Norma L.$vArchives; Labor unions$zWashington (State); Labor unions$zWashington (State)$xOfficials and employees; Labor union members$zWashington (State); Labor$zWashington (State); Labor movement$zWashington (State); AFL-CIO.$bKing County Labor Council of Washington; Central America$xPolitics and government$y1979-; Centro de la Raza (Seattle, Wash.); Office and Professional Employees International Union.$bLocal 8 (Seattle, Wash.); Records (Documents); Personal correspondence; Ephemera; Labor Archives of Washington (University of Washington); Personal Papers/Corporate Records; Labor History; Labor Unions; Civic Activism; Women; Seattle
- Norma L. Kelsey papers, approximately 1970-2010; 6231-001; 12.01 cubic feet 10 boxes
  Correspondence and subject files include materials related to Kelsey's activism with labor and social justice organizations, Central America issues, and women's and senior's issues. A substantial group of records documents Kelsey's work with El Centro de la Raza, a social service organization in Seattle. Materials from Kelsey's activities in the labor movement include records from her membership in Local 8 of the Office and Professional Employees International Union (Secretary-Treasurer, 1985-1989; President, 1989-2001), and to her work on the Executive Board of the King County Labor Council. Records of her work on a Citizens' Panel of the Seattle City Council's World Trade Organization Accountability Review Committee include interview notes, correspondence, draft documents, and reports on the preparation and planning for the WTO's ministerial meeting in Seattle in 1999. The collection also contains publications of organizations in which Kelsey was active, particularly the Puget Sound Alliance for Retired Americans and OPEIU Local 8.
  No restrictions on access.
  Donated by Norma Kelsey
  - BIOGRAPHICAL AND PERSONAL RECORDS, 1967-1994; SERIES 1 (Box-folder 1/1-1/10)
    - Biographical files, 1985-1990 (Box-folder 1/1)
    - Kelsey family documents, Undated (Box-folder 1/2)
    - Professional notes and correspondence, 1987-1994, undated (Box-folder 1/3)
    - Norma and Bob Kelsey personal correspondence, 1987-1994 (Box-folder 1/4)
    - Norma's personal file, 1967-1992 (Box-folder 1/5)
    - Norma's personal file, 1978-1989 (Box-folder 1/6)
    - Norma's personal file, 1985-1989 (Box-folder 1/7)
    - Resources for personal improvement, Undated (Box-folder 1/8)
    - Handwritten notes, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 1/9)
    - Personal notes, 1989-1991 (Box-folder 1/10)
  - CORRESPONDENCE AND SUBJECT FILES, 1974-2009; SERIES 2 (Box-folder 1/11-4/8)
    - General correspondence, 1989-2007 (Box-folder 1/11)
    - General correspondence, 1995-2002 (Box-folder 1/12)
    - General correspondence, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 1/13)
    - 1992 elections (Box-folder 1/14)
    - A Party Exploratory Committee, 1992 (Box-folder 1/15)
    - AFL-CIO, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 1/16)
    - Asian Pacific American Labor Alliance, 1999-2001 (Box-folder 1/17)
    - Asian Pacific Islander Cultural Awareness Group, 1994 (Box-folder 1/18)
    - Casa Latina, 2000 (Box-folder 1/19)
    - Cement plant, 1986 (Box-folder 1/20)
    - Central America, 1988-1991 (Box-folder 1/21)
    - Central America Peace Campaign membership, Undated (Box-folder 1/22)
    - Central America protests, 1987 (Box-folder 1/23)
    - Civil rights, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 1/24)
    - Coalition of Labor Union Women, 1974-2001 (Box-folder 1/25)
    - Coalition of Labor Union Women - Puget Sound chapter newsletter, 1984-1993 (Box-folder 1/26)
    - Colombia trade unions information, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 1/27)
    - Continental Airlines boycott, 1988 (Box-folder 1/28)
    - Criminal justice reform, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 1/29)
    - Death penalty, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 1/30)
    - Democratic Party, 2004-2006 (Box-folder 1/31)
    - Diversity / outreach, 1996, undated (Box-folder 1/32)
    - Domingo-Viernes-Jefferson Award, 2000 (Box-folder 1/33)
    - El Salvador, 1985-2001 (Box-folder 2/1)
    - El Salvador and Central America leadership tour, 1986 (Box-folder 2/2)
    - The Evergreen State College Labor Center, 1986-1994 (Box-folder 2/3)
    - Fair trade, 2001 (Box-folder 2/4)
    - Flags of convenience / Port of Seattle, 2000 (Box-folder 2/5)
    - Hands off My Neighbor symposium, 1986 (Box-folder 2/6)
    - Healthcare advocacy, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 2/7)
    - Dolores Huerta, 2000 (Box-folder 2/8)
    - Jobs with Justice, 2001 (Box-folder 2/9)
    - Kilusang Mayo Uno and Philippine activism, 1986-1989 (Box-folder 2/10)
    - Labor and politics articles and essays, 1980s (Box-folder 2/11)
    - Labor Committee for Latin American Advancement, 1996-2001 (Box-folder 2/12)
    - Labor Committee on Central American (LACCA), 1985-1989 (Box-folder 2/13)
    - Labor history, 1967-2003 (Box-folder 2/14)
    - Laborers International Union of North America (LIUNA), 2000-2001 (Box-folder 2/15)
    - Laborers International Union of North America Local 440, 1989-2004 (Box-folder 2/16)
    - Martin Luther King / King County logo change, 1999-2001 (Box-folder 2/17)
    - Mensa, 1985-1992 (Box-folder 2/18)
    - Metro-Miami Action Plan, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 2/19)
    - Mothers for Police Accountability, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 2/20)
    - National Council of Senior Citizens, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 2/21)
    - National Rainbow Coalition, 1985-1992 (Box-folder 2/22)
    - Native Americans, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 2/23)
    - Nicaragua, 1984-1987 (Box-folder 2/24)
    - Nicaragua, 1985-1991 (Box-folder 2/25)
    - Nicaragua activism, 1987 (Box-folder 2/26)
    - Nicaragua labor solidarity, 1985-1990, 2000 (Box-folder 2/27)
    - Northwest Immigrant Rights Project, Undated (Box-folder 2/28)
    - Northwest Labor and Employment Law Office (LELO), 2000-2001 (Box-folder 2/29)
    - Nuclear arms race, 1984 (Box-folder 2/30)
    - Oxfam, c. 1985 (Box-folder 2/31)
    - Leonard Peltier, 2000 (Box-folder 2/32)
    - Persian Gulf crisis, 1991 (Box-folder 2/33)
    - Philippine Workers Support Committee, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 2/34)
    - Philippines, 1989-2001 (Box-folder 2/35)
    - Norma and Bob Kelsey personal writings and poetry, 1989-1994, undated (Box-folder 2/36)
    - Poems, 1987, undated (Box-folder 3/1)
    - Political Rights Defense Fund, 1987 (Box-folder 3/2)
    - Politics (Washington State), 1992-2009 (Box-folder 3/3)
    - Port of Seattle, 2001 (Box-folder 3/4)
    - Press clippings, 1982-2009 (Box-folder 3/5)
    - Pro-union materials, 1985-1990 (Box-folder 3/6)
    - Puget Sound Alliance for Retired Americans, 2004-2009 (Box-folder 3/7)
    - Ronald Reagan, 1980-1987 (Box-folder 3/8)
    - Religious / Labor Coalition, 1998-2000 (Box-folder 3/9)
    - Sally Riccobono, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 3/10)
      Restrict: privacy issues
    - Paul Robeson, 2001 (Box-folder 3/11)
    - Salvadorean Labor Defense Network, 1987-1989 (Box-folder 3/12)
    - Ricardo Sanchez campaign for Seattle City Council, 1987 (Box-folder 3/13)
    - Seattle Times strike, 2001 (Box-folder 3/14)
    - Seattle Worker Center, 1991 (Box-folder 3/15)
    - Service Employees International Union Local 775, 1989-2007 (Box-folder 3/16)
    - Service Employees International Union Local 775, 2003 (Box-folder 3/17)
    - Service Employees International Union Local 775 bargaining information, 2003 (Box-folder 3/18)
    - Shoreline Community College / University of Washington, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 3/19)
    - SOA Watch, 1999 (Box-folder 3/20)
    - Social Security reform, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 3/21)
    - South Africa, 1987 (Box-folder 3/22)
    - Soviet Union, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 3/23)
    - Speakers bureau / media relations, 1987-1991 (Box-folder 3/24)
    - Summer School for Trade Union Women, 1989 (Box-folder 3/25)
    - United Farm Workers, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 3/26)
    - United Farm Workers, 1998-2000 (Box-folder 3/27)
    - Washington State Communist Party USA convention, 2001 (Box-folder 3/28)
    - U.S. Nicaragua sister city conference, 1987 (Box-folder 3/29)
    - Washington Citizen Action, 2000 (Box-folder 3/30)
    - Washington Federation of State Employees Local 435, Fred Hyde, 2002 (Box-folder 3/31)
    - Washington State Alliance for Retired Americans convention, 2007 (Box-folder 3/32)
    - Washington State Labor Council AFL-CIO 1991 convention (part 1 of 3) (Box-folder 3/33)
    - Washington State Labor Council AFL-CIO 1991 convention (part 2 of 3) (Box-folder 3/34)
    - Washington State Labor Council AFL-CIO 1991 convention (part 3 of 3) (Box-folder 3/35)
    - Washington State Labor Council AFL-CIO, 1985-1993 (Box-folder 3/36)
    - Washington State Labor Council Organizers' Committee materials, c. 1999 (Box-folder 3/37)
    - Washington Women United, 1986 (Box-folder 3/38)
    - White House Conference on Aging (part 1 of 3), 2005 (Box-folder 3/38)
    - White House Conference on Aging (part 2 of 3), 2005 (Box-folder 4/1)
    - White House Conference on Aging (part 3 of 3), 2005 (Box-folder 4/2)
    - White House Conference on Aging -- Washington State delegation, 2005 (Box-folder 4/3)
    - Women and labor / politics, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 4/4)
    - Worker advocacy data, 1988 (Box-folder 4/5)
    - Workers, Unions and Electronic Surveillance Conference, 1986 (Box-folder 4/6)
    - World Trade Center mobilization, 1999 (Box-folder 4/7)
    - Artifacts and ephemera, 1975-1999 (Box-folder 4/8)
    - RECORDS OF EL CENTRO DE LA RAZA ACTIVITIES, 1985/2004; Subseries A (Box-folder 4/9-5/12)
      - El Centro de la Raza, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 4/9)
      - El Centro de la Raza, 1987 (Box-folder 4/10)
      - El Centro de la Raza, 1988 (Box-folder 4/11)
      - El Centro de la Raza, 1989 (Box-folder 4/12)
      - El Centro de la Raza, 1990 (Box-folder 4/13)
      - El Centro de la Raza, 1991 (Box-folder 4/14)
      - El Centro de la Raza (part 1 of 2), 1992 (Box-folder 4/15)
      - El Centro de la Raza (part 2 of 2), 1992 (Box-folder 4/16)
      - El Centro de la Raza (part 1 of 2), 1993 (Box-folder 4/17)
      - El Centro de la Raza (part 2 of 2), 1993 (Box-folder 4/18)
      - El Centro de la Raza (part 1 of 3), 1994 (Box-folder 4/19)
      - El Centro de la Raza (part 2 of 3), 1994 (Box-folder 4/20)
      - El Centro de la Raza (part 3 of 3), 1994 (Box-folder 4/21)
      - El Centro de la Raza, 1995 (Box-folder 4/22)
      - El Centro de la Raza, 1996 (Box-folder 4/23)
      - El Centro de la Raza, 1997 (Box-folder 4/24)
      - El Centro de la Raza (part 1 of 3), 1997-1998 (Box-folder 5/1)
      - El Centro de la Raza (part 2 of 3), 1997-1998 (Box-folder 5/2)
      - El Centro de la Raza (part 3 of 3), 1997-1998 (Box-folder 5/3)
      - El Centro de la Raza (part 1 of 2), 1998 (Box-folder 5/4)
      - El Centro de la Raza (part 2 of 2), 1998 (Box-folder 5/5)
      - El Centro de la Raza, 1999 (Box-folder 5/6)
      - El Centro de la Raza, 2000 (Box-folder 5/7)
      - El Centro de la Raza, 2001 (Box-folder 5/8)
      - El Centro de la Raza, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 5/9)
      - Grievances with Head Start program, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 5/10)
      - El Centro de la Raza community campaign, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 5/11)
      - Roberto Maestas, 1999 (Box-folder 5/12)
    - RECORDS OF KING COUNTY LABOR COUNCIL ACTIVITIES, 1991/2003; Subseries B (Box-folder 5/13-6/18)
      - King County Labor Council, 1991-1994 (Box-folder 5/13)
      - Campaign for election to King County Labor Council Board, 1994 (Box-folder 5/14)
      - King County Labor Council, 1997 (Box-folder 5/15)
      - King County Labor Council, 1998 (Box-folder 5/16)
      - King County Labor Council, 1999 (Box-folder 5/17)
      - King County Labor Council (part 1 of 3), 2000 (Box-folder 5/18)
      - King County Labor Council (part 2 of 3), 2000 (Box-folder 5/19)
      - King County Labor Council (part 3 of 3), 2000 (Box-folder 5/20)
      - King County Labor Council (part 1 of 4), 2001 (Box-folder 5/21)
      - King County Labor Council (part 2 of 4), 2001 (Box-folder 5/22)
      - King County Labor Council (part 3 of 4), 2001 (Box-folder 5/23)
      - King County Labor Council (part 4 of 4), 2001 (Box-folder 5/24)
      - King County Labor Council, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 6/1)
      - King County Labor Council Bylaws Committee (part 1 of 2), 1999-2000 (Box-folder 6/2)
      - King County Labor Council Bylaws Committee (part 2 of 2), 1999-2000 (Box-folder 6/3)
      - Organizing Committee / campaigns, 1998-2000 (Box-folder 6/4)
      - Political organizer position, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 6/5)
      - Mobilization Committee, 2001 (Box-folder 6/6)
      - Workers Memorial Subcommittee, Undated (Box-folder 6/7)
      - Steve Williamson campaign, 2000 (Box-folder 6/8)
      - Committee on Political Education (COPE) (part 1 of 2), 1998-2000 (Box-folder 6/9)
      - Committee on Political Education (COPE) (part 2 of 2), 1998-2000 (Box-folder 6/10)
      - Candidate interviews / election endorsements (part 1 of 2), 2000 (Box-folder 6/11)
      - Candidate interviews / election endorsements (part 2 of 2), 2000 (Box-folder 6/12)
      - King County Labor Council Political Action Committee, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 6/13)
      - King County Union Retirees Council, AFL-CIO, 1993 (Box-folder 6/14)
      - King County Union Retirees Council, AFL-CIO, 1998 (Box-folder 6/15)
      - King County Union Retirees Council, AFL-CIO, 1999 (Box-folder 6/16)
      - King County Union Retirees Council, AFL-CIO, 2000 (Box-folder 6/17)
      - King County Union Retirees Council, AFL-CIO, 2001 (Box-folder 6/18)
    - RECORDS OF OFFICE AND PROFESSIONAL EMPLOYEES INTERNATIONAL UNION ACTIVITIES, 1984/2013; Subseries C (Box-folder 6/19-7/30)
      - Office and Professional Employees International Union Local 8, 1986-1989 (Box-folder 6/19)
      - Office and Professional Employees International Union Local 8, 1990 (Box-folder 6/20)
      - Office and Professional Employees International Union Local 8, 1991 (Box-folder 6/21)
      - Office and Professional Employees International Union Local 8, 1992 (Box-folder 6/22)
      - Office and Professional Employees International Union Local 8, 1993 (Box-folder 6/23)
      - Office and Professional Employees International Union Local 8, 1994 (Box-folder 6/24)
      - Office and Professional Employees International Union Local 8, 1997 (Box-folder 6/25)
      - Office and Professional Employees International Union Local 8, 1998 (Box-folder 6/26)
      - Office and Professional Employees International Union Local 8, 1999 (Box-folder 6/27)
      - Office and Professional Employees International Union Local 8, 2000 (Box-folder 6/28)
      - Office and Professional Employees International Union Local 8 (part 1 of 2), 2001 (Box-folder 7/1)
      - Office and Professional Employees International Union Local 8 (part 2 of 2), 2001 (Box-folder 7/2)
      - Office and Professional Employees International Union Local 8, 2002-2007 (Box-folder 7/3)
      - Office and Professional Employees International Union Local 8, 2006-2013 (Box-folder 7/4)
      - Coalition to Save Local 8, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 7/5)
      - Coalition for the Future of Local 8, 1985 (Box-folder 7/6)
      - Grievance Appeals Committee, 1993-1999 (Box-folder 7/7)
      - Membership Action Committee, 1991 (Box-folder 7/8)
      - Organizing Committee, 1986-1997 (Box-folder 7/9)
      - Political Action Committee, 1993-1999 (Box-folder 7/10)
      - Executive Board retreat, 1991 (Box-folder 7/11)
      - Local 8 Constitution and Bylaws, 1999 (Box-folder 7/12)
      - Financial information, 1984-1991 (Box-folder 7/13)
      - Budget records (part 1 of 3), 1991-1992 (Box-folder 7/14)
      - Budget records (part 2 of 3), 1991-1992 (Box-folder 7/15)
      - Budget records (part 3 of 3), 1991-1992 (Box-folder 7/16)
      - Policies, procedures and process improvement, 1982-1999 (Box-folder 7/17)
      - Union Representative interviews, 1998 (Box-folder 7/18)
      - "Leadership that Works" coalition, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 7/19)
      - Local 8 elections, 1985-1990 (Box-folder 7/20)
      - Local 8 elections protest, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 7/21)
      - Officer elections, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 7/22)
      - Local 8 elections protest, 2001 (Box-folder 7/23)
      - Fremont Public Association dispute, 1990 (Box-folder 7/24)
      - Office and Professional International Union Locals 8 and 23 staff agreement negotiations, 1989-1995 (Box-folder 7/25)
      - Contract with Office and Professional International Union locals, 1990-1993 (Box-folder 7/26)
      - Trade Section master agreement, 1998-2001 (Box-folder 7/27)
      - Trade Section contracts, 2007-2013 (Box-folder 7/28)
      - Teresa Shannon grievance, 1998-2000 (Box-folder 7/29)
      - Union ephemera, 2004, 2006 (Box-folder 7/30)
    - RECORDS OF PUGET SOUND ALLIANCE FOR RETIRED AMERICANS ACTIVITIES, 2000/2008; Subseries D (Box-folder 7/31-8/3)
      - Puget Sound Council of Senior Citizens, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 7/31)
      - Puget Sound Alliance for Retired Americans, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 7/32)
      - Puget Sound Alliance for Retired Americans, 2005 (Box-folder 8/1)
      - Puget Sound Alliance for Retired Americans, 2006 (Box-folder 8/2)
      - Puget Sound Alliance for Retired Americans, 2007-2008 (Box-folder 8/3)
    - RECORDS OF WORLD TRADE ORGANIZATION ACCOUNTABILITY REVIEW COMMITTEE ACTIVITIES, 1999/2001; Subseries E (Box-folder 8/4-9/15)
      - World Trade Organization Ministerial Meeting: protest organizing (part 1 of 2), 1999 (Box-folder 8/4)
      - World Trade Organization Ministerial Meeting: protest organizing (part 2 of 2), 1999 (Box-folder 8/5)
      - Press clippings and downloads, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 8/6)
      - Public Safety Committee / World Trade Organization conference / operation guide (part 1 of 2), 1999 (Box-folder 8/7)
      - Public Safety Committee / World Trade Organization conference / operation guide (part 2 of 2), 1999 (Box-folder 8/8)
      - Panel 2 interview transcripts and related documents (part 1 of 3), 2000 (Box-folder 8/9)
      - Panel 2 interview transcripts and related documents (part 2 of 3), 2000 (Box-folder 8/10)
      - Panel 2 interview transcripts and related documents (part 3 of 3), 2000 (Box-folder 8/11)
      - World Trade Organization Accountability Review Committee notes, 2000 (Box-folder 8/12)
      - World Trade Organization Accountability Review Committee Panel 2, 2000 (Box-folder 8/13)
      - World Trade Organization Accountability Review Committee Panel 2 correspondence, notes and minutes, 2000 (Box-folder 8/14)
      - World Trade Organization Accountability Review Committee Panel 2 policy, 2000 (Box-folder 8/15)
      - World Trade Organization Ministerial Meeting Seattle Host Committee, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 8/16)
      - World Trade Organization Accountability Review Committee document database, 2000 (Box-folder 8/17)
      - World Trade Organization Accountability Review Committee budget, 2000 (Box-folder 8/18)
      - World Trade Organization Accountability Review Committee matrix / categories, 2000 (Box-folder 8/19)
      - World Trade Organization ARC: permits, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 8/20)
      - World Trade Organization ARC: timelines, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 8/21)
      - World Trade Organization ARC: police planning, 1999 (Box-folder 8/22)
      - World Trade Organization Conference Public Safety Committee (part 1 of 3), 1999-2000 (Box-folder 8/23)
      - World Trade Organization Conference Public Safety Committee (part 2 of 3), 1999-2000 (Box-folder 8/24)
      - World Trade Organization Conference Public Safety Committee (part 3 of 3), 1999-2000 (Box-folder 8/25)
      - WTO Accountability Review report to the Seattle City Council, 2000 (Box-folder 8/26)
      - R. M. McCarthy & Associates. An Independent review of the World Trade Organization disruptions in Seattle, Washington Nov. 29 - Dec 3, 1999, 2000 (Box-folder 8/27)
      - Paul Richmond / National Lawyers Guild. Bringing in an undemocratic institution brings an undemocratic response, 2000 (Box-folder 8/28)
      - American Civil Liberties Union of Washington. Out of control: Seattle's flawed response to protests against the World Trade Organization, 2000 (Box-folder 9/1)
      - Proposed City of Seattle legislation on events and civil emergencies, 2001 (Box-folder 9/2)
      - Seattle Police Department after-action report / World Trade Organization Ministerial Conference, 2000 (Box-folder 9/3)
      - Citizen group's response to Seattle's civil emergency and World Trade Organization accountability review, 2000 (Box-folder 9/4)
      - Washington Council on International Trade response to World Trade Organization report, 2000 (Box-folder 9/5)
      - World Trade Organization Accountability Review Committee Preparations and Planning Panel final report - final draft, 2000 (Box-folder 9/6)
      - World Trade Organization Accountability Review Committee Preparations and Planning Panel report, 2000 (Box-folder 9/7)
      - Report to the Seattle City Council World Trade Organization Accountability Review Committee by the Citizens Panel on World Trade Organization Operations, 2000 (Box-folder 9/8)
      - World Trade Organization Panel 2: questions (part 1 of 2), 2000 (Box-folder 9/9)
      - World Trade Organization Panel 2: questions (part 2 of 2), 2000 (Box-folder 9/10)
      - World Trade Organization Panel 2: matrix, 2000 (Box-folder 9/11)
      - World Trade Organization Panel 2: report draft information (part 1 of 3), 2000 (Box-folder 9/12)
      - World Trade Organization Panel 2: report draft information (part 2 of 3), 2000 (Box-folder 9/13)
      - World Trade Organization Panel 2: report draft information (part 3 of 3), 2000 (Box-folder 9/14)
      - World Trade Organization N30 protest anniversary, 2000 (Box-folder 9/15)
    - PUBLICATIONS, 1980/2010; SERIES 3 (Box-folder 9/16-10/14)
      - AFL-CIO. Common sense economics: a group study manual / facilitator's guide (part 1 of 2), 1997 (Box-folder 9/16)
      - AFL-CIO. Common sense economics: a group study manual / facilitator's guide (part 2 of 2), 1997 (Box-folder 9/17)
      - AFL-CIO. Common sense economics basic workshop instructor's guide, 1998 (Box-folder 9/18)
      - O.P.E.I.U. Local 8 Newsletter, 1983-1986 (Box-folder 9/19)
      - Local 8 OPEIU Journal, 1986-1990 (Box-folder 9/20)
      - Local 8 OPEIU Journal, 1991-1994 (Box-folder 9/21)
      - Local 8 OPEIU Journal, 1995-1999 (Box-folder 9/22)
      - Local 8 OPEIU Journal, 2000-2010 (Box-folder 9/23)